And so, Defendant Jolyne
Cujo is sentenced.
You're one interesting Chaka.
How'd you end up here?
What are you in for?
I'm innocent.
After 15 years in Green
Dolphin Street State Prison,
where she will remain under the
watchful eye of strict guards,
to pay for her crimes.
What the hell is going on here?
I wasn't expecting you
to also have an ability.
It'll be Stone Ocean,
because somehow I'm going to free
myself from the Sea of Stone.
I don't know what to do.
I'll cry and cry.
I'll cry and move on.
I'll carry on my own.
I'll turn around.
Okay?
Alright?
I'll turn around.
A survival day? Get away!
I don't wanna say
Let's try it!
One, two, three, come and find a way!
I'm on me!
I'm on me! I'm on me!
One, two, three, come and find a way!
Break out!
We're coming in your heart!
I'm not even sure I can't even know!
Break out!
Don't be any way!
I'm not sure I'm on you!
It's all about the world!
The world is a problem.
Stone Ocean.
Well, in its thread form,
it can travel far distances.
But it lacks power and is easily damaged.
It becomes strong when gathered however it
can only reach about two
meters in that state.
Could stone ocean break
through the iron bars no
that's not gonna happen
the most it could do was.
My soul energy that was brought out by the
pendant stone escaping
prison with this power is.
Not possible yet.
Before I try that I need a better
understanding of the entire prison's layout.
Hey girl with the buns.
Hello I'm talking to you.
Sorry to bug, but you got some
spare change I can borrow?
I have some if I go back to my cell,
but the call I'm on is about to run out.
I'll go get it and pay
you back when I'm done!
You think you could
maybe lend me a dollar?
It's been a while since I've
last talked to my family.
Sure, I guess.
Here?
Aw, thanks so much.
You're my hero.
I'll return it once I'm done.
Move it!
The hell do you think you're doing?
Don't you know there's a line?
What line?
I've been standing behind
that girl for 30 minutes,
waiting for her to finish
that ridiculously long call.
You're the one who wasn't in line!
Dumbass, you gotta be new.
You gotta make a reservation
to use the phones here.
Well, that's news to me.
Yeah, well, remember it next time.
By the way, the wait is
usually a month long.
Wait, seriously?
It's only supposed to be a
few minutes per phone call,
so how does the wait become a month long?
Just another one of the
seven wonders, honey.
Hey, you, let me get your
place in line, would you?
And that's why we do
things this way, got it?
I want to call her.
I want to hear her voice. Mama's voice.
Jolene!
How you doing, Sally?
Shut up and get the hell away from me!
I told you, we're finished
talking to each other!
Come on, you can't
possibly hate me forever.
I'm only here to warn you.
Believe me, what you just did was
the worst move you could have made.
Why?
You just lent a dollar to
that blonde girl, right?
Go make sure she returns it right away.
Trust, there'll be hell to pay
if you don't get that money back.
What are you saying?
Of course I'm gonna have her return it.
It's just a dollar.
Hey!
That is what I'm talking about!
It ain't just a dollar!
That kind of thinking will get you killed.
Huh?
Kay, listen to me, Jolene.
One thing you need to
learn is that lending and
borrowing money with other
prisoners is an absolute Nena.
It's something you should
never do in the aquarium.
Even if it's just a dollar. Tell me,
what do you think would happen
if you were unable to get
that dollar back from the
blonde who begged you for it?
Any idea?
You'd become like her.
Word would spread around the
place that the newcomer Jolene
couldn't even get back a mere
dollar that she lent out.
And in here, rumors spread like wildfire.
They'll keep coming back
for more, just like her.
One after another, every single day.
If you run out of money, they'll just
take everything from your body and mind.
Don't know about you, but that sure
does sound like a living hell to me.
Hey, wait a minute.
You're exaggerating.
Is that what you think?
Look at her!
She lent just a dollar, too.
Speaking of the blonde, there she is now.
She went back to her room,
but it looks like she's got no
intention of coming to pay her debt.
Trust me, everything I've
said has been for your sake.
Hi.
You got a spare minute?
Oh, hey, yeah, I'm just reading.
Apparently, this book's a masterpiece.
Have you read it?
Nuh-uh.
Anyway, about that change I lent.
Um, I, uh...
I was wondering what happened to it.
Oh, of course, hon!
One dollar, there's no way I'd forget it.
I've got the memory stored in
the old noggin, right here.
I'll get it to you later, kay?
You told me that you have
some back in your cell.
You went back, right?
So where is it?
Enough already!
Don't you ever shut up!
I said I'd get it to you later.
That obviously means I
don't have it right now.
Are you a big tightwater?
What?
By the way, while you're here, do you think
you could lend me another ten dollars?
If you do,
I'll be able to call my friend
on the outside and get him
to bring me enough money to
pay you back and then some.
Well, you have it right.
Why don't you give it to me?
What the heck?
Oh, no.
Hey, come on, let me in!
But, girl, hurry up and get out of there!
Hey, are you listening to me?
Oh, Neil, give it back!
I have a dollar, so please! Oh, yeah?
Didn't you say you'd get it later?
There's no need for you to rush.
Take your time, really.
Fine, then I'll pay you!
Five, n-n-two dollars!
It's a deal.
Sorry, but that'll be ten dollars.
Hey, it's your turn.
Go in the bathroom after her. Then wait.
Someone else will want to use it.
After that,
it's up to you whether or not you get
back the money they extorted from you.
The only person who can
get you out of this is you.
What's happening to me?
That's right.
And I'll get out of here too. Somehow.
Prisoner number FE40536.
I'll be returning to my cell,
so please unlock this door.
Noon tomorrow, a visitor will be coming
to see you, but you must not meet them.
No matter what, you absolutely
cannot go to the visiting room.
If you go, you're not the
only one who will be affected.
Something even more unfortunate
than death will occur.
Who was that boy?
And why is there a child here?
Hey, bitch!
Could you not hear me
say stand back and wait?
And stop grabbing onto
the bars! Stand back!
Please just open it! Let me out!
You listen when I say
not to grab on the bars!
Around noon tomorrow, a
visitor will be arriving,
although it's not for you, of course.
for next door. You get me?
I'm just informing you.
Oh, hey, buddy.
You might want to check yourself.
Your pants are on backwards.
So dramatic.
Sorry about yesterday, Fe40536,
but still, it's your fault for hanging
on to the bars when I said not to.
Them's the rules, you know.
I had already let go, and then
you hit me two more times. Huh?
I didn't quite catch that.
Did you say something just now?
Nuh-uh.
Anyway, is there something you need?
There's a visitor for you.
Now on your feet, I gotta cuff you.
A visitor? Who?
Is that my mama?
How the hell am I supposed to know?
Just give me your hands.
Stand on the marker in front of you.
Listen to these rules.
You've got a total of 30 minutes.
You will be allowed to hold hands, but
there will be no kissing or getting naked.
Items brought in will be
handed over after inspection.
No speaking in foreign languages either.
Depending on what's said, the
guard can cut your meeting short.
Don't move from that
spot until I tell you.
You can't go in there.
Abandon this visit and
go back to your cell.
It's not too late.
Who are you?
What's a kid like you even doing here?
Shh!
I don't know the details.
I can't explain it.
But still, in this world, something
more terrifying than death exists.
And I'm certain that it's happening
right here inside these prison walls.
So run.
Go back to your cell
while you still can't.
I can't.
Mama might be here to see me.
And all I want is to see her.
I'm sure she feels the same way.
I've got to show her I'm okay and hopefully
put her at ease if only just a little.
Take this with you consider
it a good luck charm.
All right fb 405 3 6 come in.
Is this a bone?
What are you waiting for
get your ass in here?
Jolyne, did you get the pendant
that I left behind with your mother?
Old man.
Theft of a wallet, and a car, plus a salt.
There must be some sort of mistake.
My Jolene would never...
Lucky for her, she's only 14.
She'll get a slap on the wrist.
You're going to Tokyo, right now, with
everything your daughter is going through.
Can't you at least wait till tomorrow?
What kind of father are you?
Wait, hello? Hello?
Jolene, are you listening to me?
The pendants.
That'll put me in solitary
confinement for a while.
I wouldn't have come if
I knew you were here.
Hey, get up and open the door. Hey, you!
Ah, shit.
I think I hit him too hard.
Get up, would ya?
Ah, good grief.
Jolene, listen close.
Contrary to what you might believe,
the person who framed you for murder
and put you here isn't your boyfriend,
Romeo.
John Gloria.
He's currently locked up in the
men's section of this penitentiary.
He's a veteran and a sniper
who supposedly can nail
his targets through wind
speeds at 20 meters per second.
According to an investigation,
his cataracts have caused his
vision to degrade considerably.
He's the one who plotted
everything, even that car accident.
Apparently,
John Gloria had his
henchman abduct some random
hitchhiker and throw
him in front of the car.
Everything from hiring
the money-grubbing lawyer,
the judge that's sentenced you,
and setting up that rich brat
were all orders from John Gloria.
Give me a hand here!
Have you heard of plea bargaining before?
I love you!
And so, Defendant Jolene Cujo is sentenced
to 15 years. Fifteen goddamn years!
That's for hitting me twice
yesterday, you son of a bitch!
I want to know why.
Tell me now, why the hell did this complete
stranger decide to throw me in jail?
Sit down. Answer me!
Just take a damn seat.
Listen john Gloria is after you by
putting you in this jail he can dispose of
you at any time he wants but why though
because of the blood that's running through
your veins the blood of the joestars
joestars the family
name that connects back
to us from a few hundred years ago john
Gloria holds a grudge toward this blood.
To be able to communicate something to
someone's heart is a wonderful thing,
but sometimes remnants are left over,
and those remnants are known as grudges.
Back when I was younger, I kicked the ass
of the Joestar bloodline's greatest enemy.
Jean Gloria was that man's subordinate.
He never met him in person, but I've
got no doubt that they're connected.
Even though 20 years have passed,
the blind bastard turned his
fanaticism into a motive for his grudge
this makes no sense i thought you
were supposed to be some kind of?
scholar what's all this
about enemies and grudges
all you need to understand
is that you're being
targeted right now so i'm
here to bust you out the
lobby damned have you
acquired a stand ability yet?
a stand you didn't inherit anything specific
from me but as my daughter you've got
potential did anything weird start happening
to you after you received the pendant?
i'll take that as a yes it's
known as a stand A stand, huh?
Then you've got one too!
We'll escape with it.
Got it?
Give me a break.
It's a little late to
try acting like a father!
I gotta get thrown in
prison for you to help me?
Is that how you show love?
Not that it matters.
There's no space for you in my heart!
But whatever, Pops.
I'll take in that shocking story and
that whole stand thing under advisement.
You can go on home now.
And don't come see me again.
The handcuffs!
When did they...
Who lit that SIG?
The brand is different.
The guard didn't even approach
the table in the first place.
Jolene!
Get away from that door now!
Star Platinum!
The world!
Time stop! Stop!
What the fuck, did I just get shot?
Don't move, he's begun his assault.
what does the far right of this
hallway look like are there
any windows yeah two or three
but all of them have iron bars on
them this bullet's the real
deal it's a sniper round used
primarily in long-range rifles
john Gloria definitely fired this
round wait just a second you
said that guy was an inmate in
this prison we aren't even allowed
to have pens in here is that
right rifles come in parts if
you divide the pieces you can
hide them in anything if a
subordinate When it bribes the guards,
they'll most likely allow the
items in without inspection.
Slowly but surely, you'll
have the whole damn thing.
Sure that's true, but this
is the women's prison.
There's no way he can
aim from the men's side.
Especially inside a building
like this with so many obstacles.
He can with a rifle and a special power.
In other words, Jean Gloria is
most definitely a stand user.
Look there.
What is that thing?
Don't show your face too much.
It looks like that's more
than just a piece of trash.
Yeah, but it's moving away.
It seems really light.
Like it's dancing in the wind.
Don't make any sudden moves.
Before we do anything, we need
to determine that thing's power.
It dodged it!
What did I just say?
Can it see my thread or something?
Stop raising your voice.
It's reacting to something else,
not the movement of your thread.
It's going in a completely
different direction.
So does that mean it's
reacting to that thing?
What do you call it?
You know, the stuff that the
thread's movements created.
Um, the movement of air?
So it was reacting to the air currents
in order to predict our location.
But even if he knew the location,
how did he shoot a real bullet
from the men's prison to here?
That's what I want to know.
Jolene, you survived that shot from
earlier due to pure luck and coincidence.
Don't move until we know
the mechanism of the snipes.
We clear?
Don't order me around like
I'm just a stupid child.
I know all that already.
You bitch.
F.
F .E. 40536.
Do you have any idea how much trouble
you're in for what you just did to me?
Do you?
Jolene Kujo!
Here it comes.
It's reacting to him.
I'm gonna make sure you rot
in solitary confinement.
Hey, stop moving!
Before that, I'm gonna enjoy
beating the shit out of you!
Just calm down!
Jolene, don't move away from the wall!
I know that!
Stop ordering me around!
If we don't knock this shithead out
again, we're gonna be totally screwed!
Damn you!
Who the hell do you
think you're talking to?
You filthy little whore! Jolene!
Oh, my God.
Other than he?
Although you think I smile!
Inside and all the while?
I'm wondering!
About my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.